[Music]
Welcome back. Uh our research team is
now standing by with CNBC TV18's list of
top stocks for the day. First up, let's
get a handle on all the insurance
numbers that came through. Yash, tell us
about HTFC Life. Well, uh the numbers
for HTFC life looked good as far as the
top line is concerned, but the
disappointment has come through because
of the margin performance. Uh to be
specific about the numbers, the new
business premium that came in exactly uh
a little below what the street was
anticipating. So the number that came
through was about 7272 cr. The poll that
we were working with were was about 7489
cr. Total AP was also a little ahead of
the street estimates. Retail AP again
being a little ahead of the street
estimates. But as I said, margin was uh
that little disappointment which came
through. Margins came in at 25.1% versus
the poll that we were working with of
about 25.63%. So about 50 basis points
miss as far as the margins concerned.
The stocks rallied very hard in the last
3 months and 6 months and hence that
small margin disappointment could
actually turn out to be a little bigger
than just being small as far as the
stock performance today is concerned.
Okay. All right. Yash. Uh, thanks a lot
for that. Uh, Yash, but you want to tell
us about another company as well, uh,
Lombard as well as, uh, a stock that
you're tracking.
>> Well, that's correct. Uh, so strong
numbers coming in from ICIC, Lombard,
the net earned premium that saw strong
growth of 14%, underwriting profits, uh,
underwriting losses rather, they reduced
to about 293 cr versus 346 cr on a
year-on-year basis. Operating profit
that grew by about 30% at about 654 cr
versus 501 cr and importantly combined
ratio that saw a slight dip came in at
about 102.9 versus 102.3.
So the numbers overall for ICL lumbar
looked very strong. I'm going with green
as far as that company is concerned.
>> Got that? Uh let's talk about just dial.
Well just dial was an okay set of
numbers. Not very bad but there was
nothing to excite the street. The
company on the top line reported a
revenue growth of about 3% quarteron
quarter on a year-on-year basis. It was
a growth of about 6.2%. And that's
broadly been the growth trajectory for
the company. Um you know if you look at
it uh so this quarter year-on-year
revenue growth was 6.2%. Before that it
was about 7% before that 8.4%. So in a
way growth has slowed down but again um
you know Q1 was um it's an okay set set
of numbers. Margins have come in at 29%
slightly lower than the 28 29.8% in the
prior quarter and profits have been on
the flatter side. Paid campaigns growth
stands at 4.3% on a year-on-year basis.
Cash in the books continues to remain
healthy nearing 5,500 cr. So all in all
okay set a bit slow but even justile's
growth has slowed down to you know
single digits and now mid-s single
digits. But what about Bioon?
Well, yes, Bionic is in focus because
they've received uh approval from the US
drug regulator for insulin aspart which
is basically a bioimilar insulin which
they have been awaiting approval for uh
for a couple of years now. Now remember
that this approval is for the first and
only interchangeable biosimilar to
Novalog which exists which is basically
insulin aspart. uh this particular
insulin aspart has been available in
Europe and Canada since 2022. But
remember that Bioon had faced some
issues with regards to the USFD approval
because they received a complete
response letter for this particular
product approval for deficiencies at
their facility in Malaysia which is
where it will be manufactured. This took
place in 2022 2023 but eventually the
Bioon Malaysia plant was reinspected in
September 2024 and now uh they've
cleared any kind of queries in the CRL
and that's the reason that they've
received approval from the US FDA.
Hundred million is what they could make
on a conservative estimate depends on
the dynamics it could go up to around
$300 million for Bioon as well.
>> Okay. All right. Thank you very much for
that. PVR Inox is the next one we want
to focus on. Vamaki's got details on
this one. Vamaki, morning.
>> Good morning, Prashant. Well, not very
good news for PVR Inox and that is
because the Karnataka government has in
a draft notification proposed that movie
ticket prices should be capped at 200
rupees. Now, keep in mind that this is
only the draft notification. So, a time
of almost 15 days has been given uh to
the public to submit their feedback on
this proposed res uh you know uh
proposed regulation. uh but you know
this could be uh if this does go through
it could be a negative for PVROX and
that is because almost 40% of PVROX
screen are located in South India out of
which almost 12.3% are in the state of
Karnataka itself. Uh now keep in mind
that earlier on when PVROX did speak to
us they were betting big on the southern
market because average occupancy here is
uh above what the consolidated level for
the companies it's at almost around 30%.
Now keep in mind they had also you know
highlighted some plans to expand in the
southern markets. They were adding
almost 100 screens out of which 40% of
the screens were in the southern
markets. Uh so therefore uh you know
given this kind of gap it could put some
pressure on the revenues as well as the
average ticket prices going with the red
for PBR.
>> But I'm sure uh the industry will
challenge this. In fact a similar such
measure was implemented or announced by
the government in April of 2017. I mean
I was just reading what Karan Tanani uh
his view is. A similar measure was
implemented earlier by the Karnataka
government in April 2017 when it
introduced a cap of 200 rupees on movie
ticket prices across all theaters
including multiplexes. However, the film
exhibition industry challenged the
decision in court and in 2021 secured a
favorable verdict from the high court
which allowed exceptional pricing for
luxury and special formats. But this one
will be on the radar for sure. Dix
that's going to be interesting. Uh
Vinnie, what's the news and the
importance of this development?
>> Absolutely. So positive news coming in
for Dix this morning. What Dixinte
Techch has done couple of news flows.
One, they've acquired 51% stake in QE
India. Uh this is going to be through
primary as well as secondary investments
and QECH is among the top five camera
module suppliers globally and in the in
India, it's the largest amongst this
camera module suppliers. Now obviously
this is a significant step that comes
in. Why? because one it's that backward
integration which the company has been
focusing on and this will add value to
that smartphones backward integration
that the company has been focusing on.
Now other than that the second news flow
that also came in was that the company
is going to be forming a JV with
Chongqing which is a company which is
mainly into component manufacturing
precision component manufacturing. What
is this used for? This is actually going
to be used for components for laptops,
mobile phones, um, uh, in terms of
automotive applications etc. where they
can use these components for. Now this
is going to be a 74 to 26 JV. Dixon will
be holding 74 and the other company will
be holding uh, 26% in this JV. So
backward integration is what the company
has been focusing on and in the recent
time also they've done a lot of backward
integration. They had also made an JV
with HKC as well. So that is a focus on
a positive coming in there this morning.
>> All right, thanks a lot for that uh
Vinnie and you know I was reading a damn
note that suggested that value addition
as a percentage of their mix was at
around 15%. They're expecting it to go
to 35% by FY27. Good on you Vinnie with
regard to that pronunciation as well.
Thanks a lot for joining in. Let's wind
this down though with Ria on some stocks
in the news. Uh Ria, take it away. Well,
yes, Nigel. First up, we're keeping an
eye out on Hatway Cable after their
quarter 1 FI26 numbers. This time
around, the net profit has jumped up by
around 69% and the strong growth in net
profit has largely been driven by other
income. Margins have also been driven by
dealing in securities and not from the
core business of the company. And uh
it's important to note that the cable TV
business which drives most of the
revenue for the company uh is still uh
lossmaking on the EBIT level. So, myths
set coming in for Hatway cable. Moving
on, Zidus Life will also be in focus uh
today. They've received uh the final
approval from the US FDA for capsules
that are used to treat arthritis. The
stock expected to open in the green
today on the back of that. And the last
one is Kotak Mahindra Bank. Uh the uh
president and the chief credit officer
of the bank, Mr. Shankar has tendered
his resignation with effect from the
21st of July of this year.
>> Thank you very much for that. And uh
finally, HTB Financial, the newest kid
on the block. Let's see what their
numbers showed up. Gora.
>> Well, SSDB financial reported its Q1
numbers and let's look at it in two
perspective. On a weaker side, we saw
asset quality and disbbursement and on a
stronger side, we saw net interest
margin. So, first let's look at the
numbers. Net interest income has
increased almost by 18%, this is also
reflected in net interest margin which
expanded almost by 10 basis point. But
on the other hand, credit cost has
increased again on the back of the some
stress which is rising from the CV loan.
And that is the reason when we look at
profitability there we saw a decline of
around 2% on a year-on-year basis. Now
what company has said is that the
disbbursement slowdown and as well as
some stress in the asset quality is
because of the CV loans and on back of
this we will be watching out on other
counters as well. But what company has
also said is that the net interest
margins are likely to expand even
further and the reason being that 90 to
95% of its book is EBLR linked and with
rate cuts this will be passed on further
in the net interest margins and that is
the reason why they believe that ROAS
are going to expand. Let's not forget
that ROAS have also come down to 1.9%.
But there is an impact of the recent
funders and if we exclude that the ROS
has remained around 2%. So definitely on
the weaker side we have seen some
aspects but on the back of the positive
commentary we will be watching out on
this stock.
>> All right Goro thanks very much uh for
that. You know what you're going to do
is take a quick commercial break here,
but here's a quick recap of the stuff
that we put out in terms of stocks. ICS,
Alumba, Justile, Bioon, Dixon, Zidus
Life, and CODC Bank are stocks with some
green uh based on of course the news.
HFC live. Our HDB financial PVROX likely
to open in the red again based on new
slow halfway cable kind of flattish.